Julia Newman: "Into the Fire" Research Materials: Partial Inventory ALBA.226
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Julia Newman: "Into the Fire" Resources
  - Archival footage: "Filmoteca Archival Part 3 of 3." 60-minute U-Matic video. (Original from Filmoteca.), Sep 29, 2000 (Box 8, Item 226-189)
  - Archival footage: "1) Espana 2) Grenade Ma Grenade 3) Madrid En Flammes Tape 2 part 1 of 3." 60-minute U-Matic video., Oct 2, 2000 (Box 8, Item 226-190)
  - Archival footage: "1) Espana 2) Grenade Ma Grenade 3) Madrid En Flammes Tape 2 part 2 of 3." 60-minute U-Matic video., Oct 2, 2000 (Box 8, Item 226-191)
  - Archival footage: "1) Espana 2) Grenade Ma Grenade 3) Madrid En Flammes Tape 2 part 3 of 3." 60-minute U-Matic video., Oct 2, 2000 (Box 8, Item 226-192)
  - Archival footage: "Defenders of the Faith 1 of 2." 60-minute U-Matic video., Sep 29, 2000 (Box 8, Item 226-193)
  - Archival footage: "Defenders of the Faith 2 of 2." 60-minute U-Matic video., Sep 29, 2000 (Box 8, Item 226-194)
  - Archival footage: "The Spanish Earth." 60-minute U-Matic video., Sep 29, 2000 (Box 8, Item 226-195)
  - Interview: "Celia Greenspan A Clarkson." 60-minute U-Matic video. (Original from CBC.), 1992 (Box 8, Item 226-196)
  - Interview: "Sunday Morning Comrades 2 Celia/Adrienne Clarkson." 60-minute U-Matic video., Undated (Box 8, Item 226-197)
  - Stills: "Spanish Civil War Stills Tape 2 Reel 2." 60-minute U-Matic video., Oct 1, 1992 (Box 8, Item 226-198)
  - Archival footage: "Forever Activist." 60-minute U-Matic video., Undated (Box 8, Item 226-199)
  - Promo: "Their Cause Was Liberty." 15-minute VHS videotape., Jun 5, 2000 (Box 9, Item 226-200)
  - Promo: "Their Cause Was Liberty." 20-minute VHS videotape., Sep 21, 1999 (Box 9, Item 226-201)
  - Promo: "Their Cause Was Liberty." 15-minute VHS videotape., May 20, 1999 (Box 9, Item 226-202)
  - Video: "Their Cause wWs Liberty." 30-minute VHS., Undated (Box 9, Item 226-203)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 1 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Jul 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-204)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 2 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Jul 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-205)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 6 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Jul 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-206)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 7 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Jul 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-207)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 8 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Jul 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-208)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 9 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Jul 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-209)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 10 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Jul 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-210)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 12 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Jul 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-211)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 13 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Jul 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-212)
  - Promo: "PI/EP Their Cause was Liberty." 15-minute VHS videotape., Sep 21, 1999 (Box 9, Item 226-213)
  - Archival footage: "Adrienne Clarkson presents Bethune #2A NY." 30-minute VHS videotape. (Original from CBC.), Dec 11, 2000 (Box 9, Item 226-214)
  - Archival footage: "The Last Cause Episodes 1 & 2." 120-minute VHS videotape., Undated (Box 9, Item 226-215)
  - Archival footage: "The Last Cause Episode 3." 120-minute VHS videotape., Undated (Box 9, Item 226-216)
  - Promo: "Their Cause was Liberty." 20-minute VHS videotape., Undated (Box 9, Item 226-217)
  - Video: "Parraga Family Spain '96 [with Amaya Paraga]." 45-minute VHS., 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-218)
  - Archival footage: "Leves Avant Le Jour." 90-minute VHS videotape., Oct 7, 2000 (Box 9, Item 226-219)
  - Archival footage: "Espagne Vivra." 90-minute VHS videotape. (Original from Cina-Archives.), Aug 17, 2000 (Box 9, Item 226-220)
  - Archival footage: "Guernica Guerre D'Espagne." 150-minute VHS videotape. (Original from Cinemateque Gaumont.), Jun 27, 2000 (Box 9, Item 226-221)
  - Archival footage: "Actualite Guerre D'Espagne." 30-minute. Video Betacam SP. (Original from Cinemateque Gaumont.), Jun 27, 2000 (Box 9, Item 226-222)
  - Archival footage: "Guernica Guerre D'Espagne." 150-minute VHS videotape. (Original from Cinemateque Gaumont.), Jun 27, 2000 (Box 9, Item 226-223)
  - Archival footage: "Martha Gellhorn." 120-minute VHS videotape. (Original from BBC Omnibus.), Oct 18, 1991 (Box 9, Item 226-224)
  - Archival footage: "The Spanish Civil War." 120-minute VHS videotape., Undated (Box 9, Item 226-225)
  - Archival footage: "Our World May 21 1987, Our World Jan- May 1937 Jarama." 120-minute VHS videotape. (Box 9, Item 226-226)
  - Archival footage: "Spanish Civil War." 120-minute VHS videotape. (Original from National Archives.), Undated (Box 9, Item 226-227)
  - Archival footage: "The Spanish Earth." 120-minute VHS videotape. (Original from Nation Archives.), Undated (Box 9, Item 226-228)
  - Video: "BI '96 11." 60-minute VHS., 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-229)
  - Video: "BI '96 12." 60-minute VHS., 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-230)
  - Archival footage: "ACP Bethune #1A." 30-minute VHS videotape. (Original from CBC.), 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-231)
  - Video: "Homenaje 1996 TVE Madrid Concert." 120-minute VHS. (Box 9, Item 226-232)
  - Video: "Informe- Brigades Intl' 14 tvi." 30-minute VHS., Undated (Box 9, Item 226-233)
  - Archival footage: "Five Tom Mooney Films." 90-minute VHS. (Original from the Southern California Library for Social Research.), Undated (Box 9, Item 226-234)
  - Video: "TV Barcelona 1996." 15-minute VHS. (Box 9, Item 226-235)
  - Archival footage: "Footage from 1937." 10-minute VHS videotape. (Original from the UCLA Film and TV Archive.), Undated (Box 9, Item 226-236)
  - Archival footage: "San Diego Youth Demonstration Kern County Cotton Strike." 30-minute VHS videotape. (Original from the Southern California Library for Social Research.), Nov 15, 2001 (Box 9, Item 226-237)
  - Archival footage: "Films Spanish Civil War." 120-minute VHS videotape. (Original from the National Archives.), Undated (Box 9, Item 226-238)
  - Archival footage: "Filmoteca Espanol." 180-minute VHS videotape. (Original from Filmoteca.), Undated (Box 9, Item 226-239)
  - Video: "Spain '96 Tape 5 Amaya [Paraga] @ Jarama cemetary Tape 7 Amaya and Paragas." 60-minute VHS videotape., 1996 (Box 9, Item 226-240)
  - Interview: "Their Cause was Liberty Vienna Interview Irene Goldin Spiegel Tape 1." 60-minute VHS videotape., Nov 30, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-241)
  - Interview: "Their Cause was Liberty Vienna Interview Irene Goldin Spiegel Tape 2." 60-minute VHS videotape., Nov 30, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-242)
  - Interview: "Their Cause was Liberty Vienna Interview Irene Goldin Spiegel Tape 3." 60-minute VHS videotape., Nov 30, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-243)
  - Interview: "Their Cause was Liberty Vienna Interview Irene Goldin Spiegel Tape 4." 60-minute VHS videotape., Nov 30, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-244)
  - Interview: "Their Cause was Liberty Vienna Interview Irene Goldin Spiegel Tape 5." 60-minute VHS videotape., Nov 30, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-245)
  - Interview: "Their Cause was Liberty Vienna Interview Irene Goldin Spiegel Tape 6." 60-minute VHS videotape., Nov 30, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-246)
  - Interview: "Their Cause was Liberty Vienna Interview Irene Goldin Spiegel Tape 7." 60-minute VHS videotape., Nov 30, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-247)
  - Interview: "Their Cause was Liberty Vienna Interview Irene Goldin Spiegel Tape 8." 60-minute VHS videotape., Nov 30, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-248)
  - Interview: "Their Cause was Liberty Vienna Interview Irene Goldin Spiegel Tape 9." 60-minute VHS videotape., Nov 30, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-249)
  - Interview: "Esther Silverstein Blanc Tape 1." 60-minute VHS videotape., Apr 28, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-250)
  - Interview: "Helen Freeman Feinberg." 120-minute VHS videotape., Dec 5, 1993 (Box 10, Item 226-251)
  - Archival footage: "Spanish Civil War 1972 16mm cut work print." 30-minute VHS videotape., Mar 4, 1997 (Box 10, Item 226-252)
  - Archival footage: "Martha Gelhorn." 120-minute VHS videotape. (Original from BBC Omnibus.), Dec 4, 1991 (Box 10, Item 226-253)
  - Archival footage: "Chronicles of Hope A." 120-minute VHS videotape., Jan 23, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-254)
  - Archival footage: "Chronicles of Hope B." 60-minute VHS videotape., Jan 23, 1995 (Box 10, Item 226-255)
  - Video: "Hommage '96 Madrid TVE." 60-minute VHS., Jan 2, 1997 (Box 10, Item 226-256)
  - Archival footage: "Defenders of the Faith." 120-minute VHS videotape. (Original from Fast Images.), Sep 14, 2000 (Box 10, Item 226-257)
  - Video: "Spanish Civil War between the Wars." 30-minute VHS., Undated (Box 10, Item 226-258)
  - Video: "on line video." 60-minute VHS., 1996 (Box 10, Item 226-259)
  - Archival footage: "Veilles D'Armes 1." 120-minute VHS videotape., Jun 2, 2000 (Box 10, Item 226-260)
  - Archival footage: "Veilles D'Armes 2." 120-minute VHS videotape., Jun 2, 2000 (Box 10, Item 226-261)
  - Archival footage: "Veilles D'Armes 3." 120-minute VHS videotape., Jun 2, 2000 (Box 10, Item 226-262)
  - Archival footage: "Lincoln Brigade Footage from 1937." 10-minute VHS videotape. (Original from UCLA Film and TV Archive.), Jan 27, 1999 (Box 10, Item 226-263)
  - Archival footage: "Ione Paris." 120-minute VHS videotape., Jun 2, 2000 (Box 10, Item 226-264)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 tape 3 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Nov 1996 (Box 10, Item 226-265)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 tape 4 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Nov 1996 (Box 10, Item 226-266)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 tape 5 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Nov 1996 (Box 10, Item 226-267)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 tape 9 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Nov 1996 (Box 10, Item 226-268)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 10 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Nov 1996 (Box 10, Item 226-269)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 tape 11 Spain Nov. '96" 60-minute VHS., Nov 1996 (Box 10, Item 226-270)
  - Video: "International Brigades '96 Tape 13 Spain Nov. '96." 60-minute VHS., Nov 1996 (Box 11, Item 226-271)
  - Video: "Ruth and Hilda, Judy's 1986 and parts of 41 and 42 46 and 47." 120-minute VHS., Undated (Box 11, Item 226-272)
  - Video: "Demo Reel." 30-minute VHS., Sep 12, 1990 (Box 11, Item 226-273)
  - Archival footage: Benicasim 16mm film., Undated (Box 11, Item 226-274)
  - Archival footage: S. Schiff Part 3 Abraham Lincoln Brigade 16mm film., Undated (Box 11, Item 226-275)
  - Archival footage: Filmoteca Nacional de Espana; Prisioneros 16mm film., Undated (Box 11, Item 226-276)
  - Archival footage: Unlabeled [newsreel?] 16mm film., Undated (Item 11, Item 226-277)
  - Archival footage: Miscellaneous 1936-1937 16mm film. (Box 11, Item 226-278)
  - Archival footage: Bottcher, Gates, Thompson, Nelson, Merriman, Barsky + others 16mm film. (Box 11, Item 226-279)